On Sunday 16th April, 2017, during a Live
Service at The SCOAN, Prophet T.B. Joshua
gave a prophetic message concerning the nation,
Germany.
These were his words...
"I cover your nation with the blood of Jesus.
The nation, Germany opened their doors for
people who are in need of refuge.
Thousands of people entered their country
and they protected them.
I don't know why all these challenges they
are facing.
While we are praying, I saw a train or a station
where people gather - they should protect
it against an attack.
For the loving hands they stretched to other
nations, they do not deserve this.
They are a nation that we are proud of because
of what they died for immigrants - wonderful
blessings and care they give to the immigrants.
We continue to pray for them.
They should protect their stations, their
trains because I am seeing a similar thing
that happened in Russia last time.
I am seeing some funny people are there to
play funny.
So, we'll continue to continue to pray with
them.
Pray for them - the Lord will protect them.
Thank You, Lord!
In Jesus Christ's name!"